where health officials say two people, both unvaccinated, have died
from measles. No further details about the individuals were provided.
They are the first measles-related deaths in the US this year, which
is on track to be the worst year for measles cases since 1991. Pennsylvania
Governor Josh Shapiro today warned about the severity of the outbreak
and the rise of misinformation regarding vaccines.
There's real life consequences to scaring people
and not relying on actual doctors and actual medical professionals
to provide unbiased information to parents so that we can make reasonable
decisions for our kids, the governor added that he spoke with US
Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. who has pushed to revise the
nation's approach to vaccines. Shapiro says he was blunt with him
about the rhetoric coming from government officials.
The Trump administration is threatening to demolish the Kennedy Center